Good morning children.
Good morning my bubba.
Good morning.
Um, people on my Patreon have asked me
to do a Skillshare about apology and
accountability.
Now, people here on this internet often
times have said to me that they expect
me to do apology and accountability to
them, like to literally strangers,
and we've been told that 60% of this
internet is not even real people.
Um but nonetheless, I am an extremely
um accountable and apologetic person in
my personal life and in my professional
life. So if that is something that you
would like, know that it's coming to
Patreon.
Learning how to apologize and be
accountable is imperative to cultivating
relationships.
Right? Knowing how to accept apologies
and accountability is imperative to
cultivating relationships. Relationships
are at the core of our community
strength are at the core of our
resistance work. Right? So if we are not
able to do conflict resolution, we'll
never be able to have those aspects. And
ultimately what has been really
effective um by the oppressor is
implementing this idea that we don't
need to conflict resolve, right? That we
don't need to
know how to do repair repair and that we
don't owe each other anything, right?
right? Like that's a that's like a
constant thing that we don't owe each
other anything. And I would I would
disagree. I say, you know, ultimately um
we do owe each other things on some
basic levels and
on some more critical levels when you're
in Go ahead, ask your question, Rola.
When we're on when we're in
relationships, whether they be
professional,
personal,
intimate,
there's a different
set of um
own onus that is expected, right? And so
I think um those are things that
sometimes don't come up in
an exchange. They don't come up in a
relationship until
the conflict happens,
right?
So that's when you got to work through
the conflict. That's when there has to
be um you know and and sometimes let me
just say this and this is why when when
we have a narrative that says that
saying what the wrong is is the problem.
We completely undermine the opportunity
for us to move forward. You have to say
what the wrong is. This is why it's so
frustrating when you're in relationships
and you know that someone has a problem,
but they won't say what it is.
You know, when you're in a relationship
and you ask what's wrong and the person
is clearly indicating something is
wrong, but they won't say what it is, it
impedes repair.
So even though you may have been
wronged, it is your responsibility to
state
how you've been wronged or else don't
expect repair.
You know what I'm saying? Like that that
that's something that you have to be
mature about
because you're not going to get what
you're what you deserve if you don't
explicitly explain that.
Okay. Well, ego plays a role in both.
Ego plays a role in people's
accountability. It also plays a role in
people's
ability to state the issue. Sometimes
people be sometimes people don't feel
like they need to say what's wrong
because you should know what's wrong.
And it's like
if you're at a point where the person
should know what's wrong and you're
still there, you have now gone from
victim to volunteer.
Like
if you keep
repair, keep calling it out, keep
calling it out, keep calling it out and
it's not changing. You need to change.
You need to change your location.
I don't want to hear about the other
person
when they have already demonstrated what
they're about.
It's the same with a job.
You know, you're at this job, it's the
same issues over and over and over
again. figure out another new job or
figure out how to manage this job.
When I was on Insecure,
they were mean girls for the first two
seasons. I tried everything in my power
to
get in with them, get on with them, get
along with them. I brought them gifts. I
invited them places. I invited them to
my house. I organized a game night. You
know, I put us in a group chat. like I
did everything in my power and it
[snorts] was just like, oh, these people
just don't want to include me and so I'm
going to change my in my relationship
with this job. I'm not going to leave
the job. I'm going to change my
relationship with it. I'm going to treat
it like a job.
Okay.
I'm going to treat it like a job. Cuz
after a certain point, once you've had
the dinner and you've had the
conversations and you've verbalized and
you've done so in a respectful manner
and nothing changes,
what you going to do?
So, you're going to have to change your
relationship with the job. Many of us
want to go to work and act like we're at
home. You're not. And you know what? The
reason why you feel that way is because
we spend so much goddamn time at work
and we're not supposed to. We're not
supposed to spend that much time at
work. Why the [ __ ] are we spending more
of our time working than living? That
don't make no goddamn sense.
Someone here just said, "Name someone
you get along with." And I find that so
fascinating because y'all see me in
videos with people all the time. Y'all
see me on Views for Amanda. I literally
had my show Views from Amanda. did 100
episodes [laughter]
of me interviewing people.
So, the concept of name somebody you get
along with. I get along with my man.
That's who I get along with. I get along
with the the members of the SEAL squad.
I get along with them. Okay. I get along
with Leila Hathaway. [laughter]
I get like what what kind of question is
that? And the thing is is that y'all's
version sometimes y'all's version of get
along is name someone you will allow to
harm you.
I want you to hear that. That that's
your version of who you who do you get
along. Name someone that you'll allow to
harm you.
And the answer is no one. I don't even
talk to my mother anymore.
Nobody's going to abuse me.
Nobody is going to abuse me.
Period.
And that's just it.
There is way too much love out here to
allow yourself abuse.
It's an abundance.
I didn't make this tea. [laughter]
I didn't make this tea.
It's 7:30 a.m. I didn't make this tea.
There is so much love out here
in abundance.
Yes, my ex abused me.
So when people say who do you get along
with, the reality is also that when you
live a certain kind of way in a world
that is created um on certain measures,
you're not going
to get along
quote unquote with everybody.
period.
You're in a world that lives on toxicity
and narcissism. You're in a world that
is built on patriarchy and um
denigration, right? You're in a world
that is literally founded on lies.
So when you live in truth,
yes, taste mentalizer. So when you live
in truth,
when you live in kindness,
when you live in creativity and
sensitivity and compassion and
curiosity, those things go completely
against the structural uh the the
structural forming of this matrix.
These are such weird questions. You must
be bots.
Someone just asked me, "Do you have
friends?" Do you have close friends?
[laughter]
Like
what?
Like what are we talking about?
>> [laughter]
>> That's such a weird question.
And let me just say,
if you don't have close friends, I want
y'all to also think about that because
sometimes you may not have close
friends, not because of you, but because
of the setting you're in, the
circumstances you're in. If you live in
a small town full of MAGA [ __ ] full
of MAGA folks, right, and you somehow
manage to fortify your critical thinking
skills,
you're not going to have close friends
in your close in your small town,
right?
Like that's just the reality.
So, you're going to have to like change,
you know, your location.
Like, I was in the industry. I was in I
was in the entertainment industry and I
I I
had friends,
but even as I became a supporter of
Palestine
in a loud public way, those people that
I thought were friends demonstrated that
they are not.
That weirdo Jessica.
That weirdo Jessica just said, "Do you
have close friends?"
And then said, "You've told me
everything I need to know."
I think the other thing too is that you
all have some of you all have this idea
that I'm like
not a human
that because I come on this internet and
I speak to you because that's one of my
gifts that I am not a human
that I don't live in the world outside
of this screen and it's it's it's it's
really unfortunate for for you because
then it undermines the validity of
things I say, right? Because if I'm not
a human, then I'm not relatable. And if
I'm if I'm not relatable, then how
useful is what I am on? How useful is my
information,
you know,
but I do find that hilarious. Um
and um
I'm so fortunate to have close friends
and you know as you grow and as an adult
and become an adult you you go through
es and flows with people sometimes
you're advancing and healing
um you know faster or slower and
um and that can shift dynamics right?
That can shift dynamics. Um, you know, I
have a friend that we were roommates in
college and then we were roommates out
of college and
you know, she is my sister. However,
we, you know, we've had some bumps in
the road
just because of life and just different
ways of looking at
scenarios, situations, not politically,
but situations. And
right now, we're like in an upswing. And
it's just really nice. And, you know,
the upswing ends up really being more so
about like her communiciveness.
Um cuz I'm only going to like re I'm
only going to reach out so many times
and then it's like okay well you're
clearly busy or whatever whatever.
And um you know also if you have friends
with ADHD
that can be tough because they have a
tough time you know kind of keeping up
communication
because of the executive function
and you also don't want to like harass
them because then that also [ __ ] with
them. Um
and so you know these are the thing
these are these are these are the things
that end up being the realities of
living in this world in this body
you know and what does that look like
you know like my man was telling me
yesterday that
he had a homeboy and he had to like cool
off being friends with him because he
was like yo like his mental health had
gotten to a point where you just didn't
know
when he was going to flip and to what
extent
and it made it like dangerous,
you know, and he wasn't like doing
anything to like deal with his health.
Deal with his health. Sorry.
So
the only thing you can do in my opinion
is remain compassionate,
remain conscious,
remain curious
and
um
keep your heart. Three stacks.
keep your heart.
You know, people are asking me like,
would I go on would I have gone on the
insecure tour if I had been invited?
Well, I think the circumstances of the
invite are very important to
acknowledge,
right?
If I'd been approached
with the context of listen, I apologize
for
my
failure to protect you as as the leader
and I understand
where we went wrong
and I would love to like start fresh.
I'm near
cuz there's like this weird positioning
of
me as somehow a problem on insecure that
has never it's never been actually
corroborated because I was not a problem
on insecure as you've seen in the
videos.
I'm a delight,
you know. But
I think that's the thing that we fail to
acknowledge that like sometimes there
isn't two sides like in terms of like
sometimes it's not like oh two people
don't get along
at the end of the day. It's just
sometimes some folks be on one.
[laughter]
I think one of my greatest qualities is
um the desire for redemptive movement.
and you know, redemptive choices, right?
The desire to
um like this is like this is an odd
thing right here. Like someone's like,
"Maybe you can extend the olive branch."
That's not my responsibility.
That that is literally not my
responsibility. [laughter]
I do not and I should not be extended to
extend an olive branch to folks who have
put me in harm. who folks to folks who
who literally did not care that I was
harmed. [laughter]
I I don't I think it's a I think it's a
reflection of your own lack of
selfworth. And I want to extend to you
that you do not need to do that.
You do not need to do that, particularly
in a working setting.
Let me tell y'all a story. Y'all want a
story?
Let me know if you want a story
cuz I'm up and I got time. So, let me
know if you want a story.
Okay, before I start my story, Miss
Daddy said, "Yep." Before I start my
story, someone asked, "When do you know
how do you know when it's time to
leave?"
Um, and how do you know when it's time
to love and leave and let be when the
challenge becomes a drain? When the
challenge becomes a stress, it's time to
go.
Sometimes things are challenging. They
challenge you to face your blind spots.
They challenge you to, you know, shift
um out of habits that you have may have
may have slipped into. They, you know,
some of us aren't narcissists, but we
were around narcissists and so we have
taken on narcissistic behaviors. And so,
you know, they sometimes that's a
challenge, right? Sometimes that's a
challenge. However, when it comes to
stress
because you're not being heard, you're
being gaslit, you're being
um manipulated, etc.
It's time to go. Okay, so here's a
story.
So,
um
a friend of mine
told me that, you know, for their
birthday they were like really they
wanted me to travel to to visit them for
their birthday um because there was like
a whole party that was happening. So
they wanted me to come to Grenada to
visit them for their birthday. Um
and um I had spoken to them the day
before his birth I had spoken to him the
day before his birthday, but then on his
birthday he no sorry I spoke to him the
day before his birthday and he was like
you know my birthday is tomorrow so I
expect you to call me tomorrow on my
birthday. Okay. So birthdays are very
important to this person. And
um Oh, I love that Claud K. And um
does the does does the relationship give
you wings or weight?
Nice.
When I tell you I'm so happy [laughter]
My [ __ ] is so dope.
[snorts]
Hold on. I'm just pausing right now
[laughter] because
he's so [laughter] awesome.
>> [gasps]
>> Man,
same Bella Soulrebel. Same.
Same.
Like we were just chilling yesterday and
I was like, "So this is it? Like it can
be like this?" He was like, "Yeah."
Like just like you're happy right now?
He was like, "Yeah."
And I was like, "We're just chilling."
I was like, "Yes,
this is the good part.
What?"
And then I was like,
"We don't have any eggs."
And he was like, "Well, my boy my boy
does sell eggs.
He sells eggs,
so let's go get them." And I was like,
"It's 11:00.
What are you talking about?"
We pulled up on his boy at 11 p.m. And
that [ __ ] gave us a tray of eggs,
[laughter]
bro.
[snorts]
Like [laughter]
what?
Casual. I was like, "Okay, but it's
11:00 p.m." And he was like, "Well,
people just come at 3:00 a.m., you know,
whatever." [laughter]
A tray. I just need to be clear. A tray
of eggs.
Bad girl. Tiffany
selling eggs by the brick. [laughter]
I was like,
"This is fascinating." [laughter]
Fascinating.
Yes. Caramel.
We talking more than a dozen. Misha, the
[ __ ] came home and made eggs.
[laughter]
It's like
you about to eat eggs right now.
Hi Posie J.
Does he cook? Taste mentalizer. That
man's a chef
literally.
So anyh who,
so my homeboy
centers his birthday
which lets you know that the birthday is
topnotch, right? It's priority.
And
so I would expect
that um
if I verbalize to you that I want to
send him my birthday that you're going
to understand.
Now again the key word here the key
phrase here is that if I verbalize to
you.
All right? Because
to verbalize
means that you have expressed
expectation
and so you're not just like
having something in your head that you
want someone to just know,
right?
So,
I tell him,
oh, Posie J, bless you.
And maybe they're just non-verbal for
now. You know,
life is long.
And sometimes some of these brains just
just need a little warming up. That's
all. They just need a little warming up.
Um,
>> so
where they come in there?
Where they coming from there?
If you see where these people come from,
I ain't know where they're coming from.
So,
>> okay.
Is that my cousin?
Okay. So, Sunish baby, that's what's up.
So, I tell
Yes, Shel's deliverance. We are.
The dogs are barking because these
people just came out [laughter] from the
bush. Okay, they're going to stop soon.
But these people just came out from the
bush and the dogs are like, "Where the
hell did y'all come from?"
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's
okay, Butchie. It's okay, babes. Yeah.
Joby,
[laughter]
I didn't name the dogs. The dogs have my
I have my names for them.
It's okay. But there you go.
If I get him to stop talking. No, these
are not my dogs. The neighbors dogs.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. We finished
with that.
So now the dog in the back start
barking.
So now they trying to out bark the dog
in the back.
Okay. So, I tell my homeboy, "Okay, for
my birthday, all I want is Bailey's and
nutmeg ice cream." And I tell him and my
home girl, and they work together. And
um and so, you know, I don't I don't
I will say this, I have a lot of
acquaintances. I'm very particular about
who I [laughter] consider friends
because a friend is someone that you can
call on when you need help. Morning.
A friend is someone you can call on when
you need help. If you cannot call on
them and they cannot call on you, they
are not your friend.
Okay?
And that's fine. You don't need a
goddamn army to call on.
Yes. The quiet code. LA. Yes, you can.
Absolutely. [laughter]
So,
um,
and and and listen, because not
everybody not everybody even is you're
not even capable to necessarily help
everybody who needs help, right? Like my
friends who have like hella kids and
[ __ ] like I I'm not really like my
acquaintances that have hella kids,
etc., etc. I am not
the best source of help for you. I'm not
um you got a husband, you got all type
of [ __ ] going on, you know, like it's
just like
respect
in the same way that like I
live a certain way and there's people in
my life that like
isn't really um they aren't really
aligned with me.
It's not to say they're not my friends.
I mean, it's not to say they're not my
people. It's not to say I don't like
them. They're just not my friends.
Anywh who, so um
when this person when I did arrive for
my birthday, sorry, when my birthday did
arrive, when my birthday did arrive, I
um ran I saw them and I was like, "So,
you know, what are we doing?" And they
were like, "Oh, well, our home girl has
it planned. We don't I I don't know. I
don't actually know." And I was like,
"Okay." Cuz that let me know that he had
removed himself from any type of
involvement in my birthday other than
just like showing up. And
I mean that was like
um
its own thing. Thank you Beyond Horizon.
Like stop telling please let people
know. Don't rush me. I'm talking. I
will. You're here. You enjoy it. You
don't enjoy it for whatever, but I'm not
working for you. Um,
so
I
was like,
"Okay, I just let that sp I just let
that pass."
And
that evening,
our mutual friend
took me
on like a little um
boat ride for my birthday.
Again, I'm just going off of what she's
organized
in the middle of a work day
where she is running the show. She still
found time to organize
a boat ride for me
and then literally like ran to the
grocery store and made a chari plate for
us and got a bottle of Bailey's.
And I know that she only did this
because I said it would matter to me.
And I am not like a big deal person.
like I don't require opulence.
Um
my love my love language is acts of
service and affection.
So
like
I don't need to go to some like
fancy restaurant. I don't need fancy
gifts or whatever. Whatever. I just like
I like a lot of things. So like I'm very
easy to please. [laughter]
like
um
you know so
that was
like we did a sunset ride on a boat. It
was an hour. I'm good. [laughter]
So after the boat ride, we get in the
car and she called homeboy because we
were going to have a little dinner and
she called homeboy and his he answered
the phone and he didn't know I was on
speaker and he said well y'all weren't
here so I left
and I was like
um but you didn't even like call or text
to see like what's good and he said Oh.
Oh.
Um,
it's your birthday. You don't need to
worry about logistics.
And so we were 15 minutes behind
and we went
to the place for dinner,
which was very convenient for him.
And um he showed up an hour later
and I had two other friends that had
come.
And
when he showed up an hour later, we had
already cuz we had made a table for six
and then my other home girl, she
couldn't make it. And then this guy
wasn't coming. So we just broke down the
table to a table for four. And so when
he showed up, he didn't show up in
apology. He showed up. Um, and I want
you to listen for the whole story. Okay?
I want you to listen for the whole
story. He showed up and was like, "Hey,
it's the birthday girl. It's the
birthday girl, Amanda."
And
for me, I was not enthused by that
because I feel like you can show up and
just be like, "I'm so sorry. My fault.
I'm I know it's an hour late." So, when
you show up acting like you're not an
hour late, it just rubs me the wrong
way. It's just not indicative of
somebody that is an acknowledgement of
the the room.
No, no nutmeg ice cream.
And so
my face was just like
I said, "This is really tacky." And he
was like,
"Well, why?" I mean, are you serious?
So, I want to tell y'all something.
If you know, okay, cuz you know, if you
know,
if you know, cuz you know, you be
knowing. If you know
that you done did some corny [ __ ] and
someone brings it to you and you
respond, are you serious?
You are deflecting.
It's not okay.
my home girl and I
I had like snapped on her about
something
and
I really didn't know if it bothered I
don't I didn't know what extent it
bothered to her. I didn't know what
extent it bothered her, but I did know
that I had snapped on her.
Okay.
Um,
and so we ended up going to lunch like
two days later
and at lunch she was like, "You know, I
just want to share with you
that when you snapped on me the other
day, it really like threw me off."
In that moment,
if I had said, "Damn, it threw you off."
She should not [ __ ] with me no more.
She shouldn't [ __ ] with me no more
because she and I both know I snapped on
her.
She's now telling me how it affected
And in that moment, I had to [ __ ]
take accountability.
And let me also add, for some of us, in
the moment, accountability is also not
even our best. So, you may have to come
follow up.
I know you may have to do a follow-up
apology, which I had to do because in
the moment I was like really embarrassed
that I had
behaved that way and I was also really
sorry that I had hurt her feelings.
So, in the moment, I was also dealing
with my own feelings and really working
to not let my own feelings impede my
acknowledgement of her feelings,
right? However, doing that work
simultaneously is is not going to be the
best version of an apology. It's just
not.
And so, I I did the best I could in that
moment and then I slept on it. And then
the next morning, I was able to give her
the full 100% apology that's all about
her because I had worked through my own
[ __ ]
you know? And I and I had to share with
her like, yo, like I you're right. And I
I really realized like that that
behavior is reflective of, you know,
things that I've carried from other
people and I need to make it my business
to remove that
from my repertoire. [laughter]
Right? So
this is just my this is just an example
that I'm sharing of my own experience of
having to you know take accountability
and apologize.
So to go back to the story I was telling
before when I said
this is tacky
and
his response was
damn
are you for real?
That's not okay.
you know that's not okay.
And
um
you know Ambria the realtor said I hurt
her feelings and something I want to
remind you all is like
you all are having a parasocial
relationship with me.
I don't know you.
You're you're you're a picture that I
don't even know if it's real.
you're a name that I don't even know if
it's real.
So, when you all have these feelings
about me,
um,
often times I feel like it's an
imbalanced
relatability.
Um,
so to the story,
he got very defensive.
Well, Fatima, that's different. I've
like been talking to you on lives and
[ __ ] for years now. Like, damn near two
years. Um,
so I was like, why? He, you know, he got
defensive and said
Aquarius. [snorts]
He got defensive was like, "Oh, um,
you're serious?" I said, "Yeah, I'm
serious because
you know you an hour late." He was like,
"Well, you all weren't on time either.
It doesn't matter if he was in. This is
what I need y'all to understand. It is
not your responsibility to figure out
other people's [ __ ] feelings. And I
want you to really release yourself from
this. Don't get me wrong. Sometimes it
is helpful in you not internalizing
something. However, in that moment, it
is not my responsibility to now protect
his feelings when he is not protecting
mine.
So when someone here is like, well maybe
he was embarrassed.
Perhaps he was not my [ __ ] problem.
Not my problem.
We are all adults. We are in control of
our own emotions as we we should be in
control of our own emotions. I didn't
flip on this [ __ ] I'm not cursing him
out. I'm not yelling. I said that's
tacky. This is tacky. I am verbalizing
displeasure. And in that moment, let me
tell you what you do when your
compassion is locked in
because it's a thing when you lock in
your empathy.
When you lock in your empathy
and someone tells you that your behavior
is like not it
and you know for a [ __ ] fact
that you aren't the onus,
you ask to step aside.
You ask to step aside
when a friend shares with you. Hey, nah,
they're not being disrespectful. Like,
it's it'd be different if I was like,
man, [ __ ] you, [ __ ] Like, cuz then,
yeah, [ __ ] me.
No, I'm not saying that. I am sharing
with you that what you thought was
working is not working. So, then you
change course,
right? You change course.
Oh, my fault.
My fault.
I'm in a new relationship. You know it's
changing course be happening.
What? We be in here like [ __ ] Mario
Kart.
Get to change course. Oh, I didn't know.
My fault. Cuz you testing. Not testing
is not the word, but like you're finding
out what people
are annoyed by, what people are
empowered by. You're finding out what
annoys You're finding out what um what
hurts people's feelings, right? You're
finding out, you know, what what builds
people up, you know? Like that [ __ ] had
to find out. Don't [ __ ] tease me,
bro.
I don't like that.
There's a certain version of I don't
teasing out like don't antagonize me.
Don't say something that you know would
upset me because I take everything
literal and I just because of my autism
like I don't typically know if you're
telling if you're being honest or not.
So don't do that.
So, you know, you got to kind of have an
openness
to the realities that you don't know
everything about everybody and that you
may have read the room wrong.
You know, you may misread
and when that happens, you got to kind
of take that out.
So, you know, I'm telling Buddy like
I didn't like that. And to then say, are
you being serious? Is is not okay.
I sure did, Keelia. And you are
hilarious for noticing that.
Thank you for buying the FAA shirt,
Happy Tara.
So
I then
So you know he was like so I said
there's not even room for you at the
table and he's like well
so you want me to leave? Yeah.
Yeah.
Mhm. And so he left
and then I never heard from him again.
So that was on July 1st. So two days
ago,
two days ago, I said, you know,
I'm going to invite the possibility for
correction
because this is someone I consider to be
my friend.
And the the the mistake people are
making about like me and Issa Ray is
that we're friends.
We are acquaintances. We worked on a
show together.
That is not my friend.
I I mean I have
I have called Issa to help me um when I
was in a bind with uh with Hurricane
Harvey and I was trying to help some
folks. Um sh I was trying to help get
some supplies shipped with Hurricane
Harvey and I remember calling Issa to
see if she could um I forgot what the
specific reason was why but but she did.
She did help, but beyond that, like
we're not friends. I've never been to
her house. She's never been to my house.
We don't hang out,
you know. So, um I am an employee.
And my my gripe is as an employee
to be clear. My gripe is as an employee.
So when people say things like,
you know, you all should um be you all
should bury the hatchet, etc., I'm like,
my gripe is as an employee.
Okay? So when people say you should
extend an olive branch, my gripe is as
an employee.
[laughter]
Okay?
Period.
So,
back to the homeboy as friends.
As friends,
I said, I'm going to extend
an olive branch of clarity
cuz perhaps he doesn't know why I'm
upset.
And let's be real, sometimes men, they
just aren't necessarily as
intuitive or perceptive.
So, I sent a voice note
and I said, you know, I want to just
give you some clarity
on why I have eye because I do believe
you to be a good person. And so I just
want to explain my er
and I said you know my er is grounded in
the fact that our friendship has been
solely on your terms and the one time
that you had an opportunity to show up
on my terms
um you you you didn't
every other instance has been based on
your terms and your version of
generosity. And there's a difference
between generosity and sharing.
Generosity is having surplus and
extending it. And it's beautiful, right?
But sharing is when you don't have
surplus and you still carve out enough
to share because you know it will
benefit the other person.
And sharing is what's required for
friendship and community. Generosity is
lovely. However, generosity does not
beget community.
And that is why side note when people
talk about billionaires doing
philanthropic work it is not the [music]
same as community
giving away surplus
is not the same as giving away what
you've got.
Okay. So when you see me giving away my
time, when you see me doing free shows,
when you see me giving away free product
that I have paid for,
that is not surplus. That is sharing.
That is building community within my
means
and it says it it indicates
something. You know, sometimes you you
know, when we talk about actions
speaking louder than words, I just want
to say that even if actions speak louder
than words, if you can't interpret the
actions, then they're kind of useless.
So, like for instance, like my man is
not as
verbally expressive as I am. And so,
I've had to like start learning how to
interpret his actions. So, one of the
things I've started doing is like I'll
ask like, "So, is this action this? Am I
reading this properly?
So, you know, like
I did an event the other night. At the
end of the event,
I got I was leaving. He was asleep. I
called him. He He was He woke up, but
[clears throat] he was like
groggy, and I was like, "You can go back
to sleep. Like, I'm I'm just about to
go. I'm I'm on the ride home. You can go
back to sleep.
and he was like, "No."
And he fought and woke himself up to be
on the phone with me for the ride home,
which was an hour.
And I was like,
"Am I am I interpreting this action
properly that this is an act of service
and a show of love?" He was like, "Yes,
I killed sleep for you."
Got it. Thank you.
Now I know
like
[clears throat]
no K Taylor I have not always DJ
Faithful Jewels. The fact that you said
one word and I already know what you're
saying is
hilarious.
[laughter]
I love black people.
I love I love us.
They said one word, Savannah. I know the
whole context. I know all of it.
[laughter]
I love us.
I [ __ ] love us.
Savannah.
So, I have not always been a a good
communicator. Um, some of the reasons I
wasn't a good commun communicator is
because I was raised by a covert
narcissist. So, my mother herself was
not a good communicator. She was not an
emotionally intelligent person. So, she
was a great provider. She was somebody
who um
understood her daughter on like a
needs level um but was not able to meet
me on an emotional level. And so
therefore like I was lacking that
ability to ever to be able to like
um live in my feelings the way that I
wanted to. Right. And so
it's taken time and learning and um
reading and practice
um to
be able to and let me also say it's also
changed it's also taken changing friends
right arriving at a friend group that
receives communication because if you
have friends that can't communicate the
way that
emotional intelligence requires it's not
going to work.
It's not going to work.
I I hate to break it to you. You got to
love him and let them go.
So, I sent the voice note to my homeboy
because I am a communicator and
ultimately I always want redemption. I
always want us to come together.
Stop asking me the same question over
and over again. Um,
and so I sent the voice note and I said,
you know, I just feel like our
friendship has always been on your terms
and whenever you ask me to spontaneously
hang out, I'll do it. And, you know, to
be quiet, to be to be honest, like
I wasn't
always necessarily like down, but like
you want to hang out and I'm here, like
let me let me go. Let's let's you know,
let me let me make time. Let me make
space. And so to hear someone say, "You
weren't on time, so I went and did
something else." That's a crazy comment
to come from a friend,
particularly on a birthday.
and you already know that they highly
regard birthdays.
You know, it's cuz for some people
birthdays really aren't that big a deal.
To be quiet, to be quite honest, for me,
The only reason I was doing something
for my birthday was because they were
like, "We should do something for your
birthday."
So, here I am like complying.
And so I left the voice note and I ended
the voice note by saying,
you know, I just wanted to express this
to you so that you have all the
information and then you can choose
whether or not you want to go forth,
whether you want to make amends, whether
you want to um you know, [clears throat]
I forgot the exact wording I use, but
essentially like whether whether you
want to reach out to to course correct
And yes, Iman. And um and I ended with
love you.
His response
was to send me a text that said,
"I am open to having a conversation.
However, I do not consider voice notes
to be a a valid to be a a useful source
for communication.
Please let me know
um I if you would like we can converse
at some point this week at a time
convenient for you.
I said
you were doing in this comment in this
text you're doing exactly what I said
in the group in I said you're doing in
this text exactly what I said in the
voice note stay up
you think so Iman on
such a it was such an HR response
cuz also in the voice note I said the
way that you're managing this makes me
feel like you don't care for me the same
way I don't care for you.
So that's the end of that.
[laughter]
That's the end of that.
You know,
and I'm just going to throw this out
here.
Your urgency in correcting a problem
with a friend is very important. And you
can take that as you wish. But I've I I
I am a believer
that the immediiacy with which you
address something is very important.
Pick up a phone.
If you send me an essay text, I'm
calling you immediately.
If you send me a a voice note podcast,
I'm calling you immediately.
the response that I feel would have been
far more far more um
engaging
would have been even if they couldn't
talk in that moment would have been to
say I hear you thank you for sharing
your feelings with me and um just give
me a moment to process them so I can
address them properly and you know we
can
That's it.
Now, some people in here are surprised
at that being the end of a friendship.
And
again, I am 45 years old. I am not going
to do emotional labor.
We can work on each other. We can work
on ourselves alongside each other.
However, I'm not going to do emotional
labor. I'm not going to do the work of
figuring you out,
you know. But at the end of the day,
folks want people want to be seen.
That's why we've been painting art on
walls since the dawn of time. We want to
be seen.
>> Okay.
And you get you get so far by literally
just telling someone
I see you.
I hear you.
You don't communicate with someone like
that.
It still upsets you when you cut someone
off. Change your perspective. You're not
cutting them off.
They're not even attached to you.
You're just accepting that
when people are being harmful or people
are being
non-additive to your life, when people
are
um
preventing your growth, they're not
attached to you.
So you're not cutting them off.
You're just accepting
that you're attached to them.
Family are not attached to you. Nobody
is attached to you
unless they want to be. You choose how
people are attached to you.
Iman, I was not I was actually bigging
him up the whole the whole uh
the whole live because I'm sitting here
drinking tea that I didn't make.
No, you choose who's attached to you.
You know,
the only person you're attached to is
your mother at birth.
Everything else is just proximity.
I mean, KBC20, I did a lot of work over
the past few years trying to deal with a
mother who is emotionally unintelligent.
Um, first, you know, expressing my
desire that they go to
therapy and and, you know, then,
you know, trying to then mitigate our
time by, you know, choosing just certain
conversations and not really venturing
into certain waters. Then mitigating our
conflicts by, you know, choosing certain
settings and, you know, cultivating
distance, etc., etc.
And um you know eventually it just got
to a point where the emotional intellig
the lack of emotional intelligence
turned into not turned into it just it
consisted to it consisted to persist as
emotional and verbal abuse and I just
decided
that this is not somebody who is
attached to me.
I accepted that
because I want you to think of it this
way. Okay, let me let me reframe it.
You're on a path, right? We're we're I
know that in this life I arrived here
with a destiny. Not everybody has that
experience. However, my soul did arrive
here with a destiny. I'm pulled by a
string and I know when I'm off my path
because I literally can feel it. I can
feel the tautness of the string. It's
discomfort. When I'm on my path, I don't
feel the string.
Okay?
So, that's my experience. That's my
soul's experience. Everyone's soul is
having different experiences. Some are
having that same experience. Others are
just showing up here for the first time.
That being said,
we are on a path.
We're having some type of human
experience. In that process of human
experience, in this realm, we move
linear.
Okay?
Keep up with me. In this realm, we move
linear.
So, even if we have some steps backs,
etc., we are still moving linear. We're
moving from A to B. Our bodies age
biologically from A to B. So we're
having exactly a somatic experience.
Okay.
So
when you're moving
in a linear form,
folks are either moving at your pace or
they're not.
You have to move at your soul's pace.
When we say march to the beat of your
own drum, that's what that means. It
doesn't just mean being like a zany
individual. It means moving at the pace
at your soul's pace.
Your energy rhythm. Energy is rhythm.
Energy is rhythm.
Right? Rhythm comes back around. Right?
So your soul's energy rhythm is your
pace.
You're moving at your own pace. Your
energy's rhythm. So folks who are around
with you and align with you align with
that rhythm. It's like when I'm making
beats,
things have to align or else they don't
work.
So in that rhythm,
when you're moving,
if you have people who are not on rhythm
with you, it [ __ ] up your rhythm.
So we're not cutting people off,
we're restoring our rhythm.
And they can come into your rhythm
if they can get in tune with themselves.
And sometimes
it's never going to happen because their
rhythm just ain't on with on with you.
So, I don't want you to think of it as
cutting off because that feels violent
in a way that blames the victim,
right? Cuz like
why are you having to Dreb O1 say he has
no rhyme, no rhythm? Well, do you have
do you do you have a heartbeat or do you
have an arhythmia?
So I I want us to change that language.
You're not cutting someone off when it's
because they are disrupting your rhythm.
You're simply saying like we are not in
alignment. I just recently did this with
somebody.
I love them. I think they're a great
person. We were no longer in alignment.
And that's it.
>> [laughter]
>> tonight.
That's it.
You know, I have told my mother what
would be required of her
to be in rhythm with me. She has chosen
not to do that.
What can you do?
You know what can you do?
You mourn, you move,
stay in rhy with them. I met a woman at
the airport yesterday. We were sitting
next to each other on the same flight
and she said, "Um,
eventually I complimented her hair, her
hair,
cuz I like your haircut." And when I
complimented her haircut, she was like,
"Are you Amanda Seals?" And I said,
"Yes."
And she said, "My daughter really liked
you."
My daughter really liked you. She just
passed away on July 1st.
And I immediately held her hand
and I said, "You know, July 1st is my
birthday. How are you feeling?"
And we had a really nice talk about her
daughter. Her daughter was 48 and she
died of um sarcidosis, I believe. And I
might be mispronouncing that. And um
you know she was like you know she was
sick for a while so you know this was a
path that we got to go on and
um she said but you know I had 48 years
of her and I'm just really blessed that
I got to be with her for 48 years
and
it was very moving to see how at peace
she was with her daughter's passing
because
of course like you would grieve and you
would harm I mean feeling feel like you
would you would grieve and feel like
pain. Um and she was like, you know, I
have two granddaughters
and
I will just continue
um
with them.
And it was really beautiful like to have
that exchange with her. I held her hand
the whole time and I really appreciate
that she let me hold her hand.
[laughter]
Um,
then I went to board the plane and when
I was boarding the plane, this woman was
livid at her tweenager. She looked about
12, 13 and she was literally like
yelling at, okay, she wasn't yelling at
her, but she was scolding her loudly
in front of everybody. She was like,
"You are embarrassing me. You are
embarrassing me."
And
Miss Debbie
and
I could tell that the teenager was like
affected. Hey, Sarah.
And
the mom, she just looks so frustrated.
So then we're boarding the plane and she
like yelled at the son now.
And I just I turned around. I said, "Are
you okay, love?" And she was like, "I'm
just very stressed. I'm just very
stressed." And um they were trying to
like like the the carry-on
the carry-on was causing an issue. So I
just took the carryon, y'all.
Give me that. Just took the carryon.
I took the carryon. I said, "Take some
deep breaths, sis. Let's take some deep
breaths. Take some deep breaths." You
know, listen, everyone doesn't go along
with it when you do this. Let me just
tell you.
She did.
She took some deep breaths and I just
handled the carryon for the from that
point forward.
I just removed the issue
and thankfully no flight attendant
looked at me crazy when I boarded with
two carryons.
But you know, so okay, some might say
that's none of your business, etc., etc.
What I need y'all to really, really
understand, and we can take this to
Jay-Z,
we are all sharing space.
We are all sharing space.
The earth's surface is finite
to to my to our knowledge.
So in sharing space, we owe each other.
And
if you want to even get selfish with it,
somebody in distress in your space
causes you distress.
So if you can alleviate their stress,
you alleviate your own.
I got the bag. I removed the bag, which
was clearly the center of the stress.
No more problems.
It's not going to be that basic, but in
that instance, it was like, "Give me the
bag."
I was walking through the airport
yesterday. It was
unbelievable how crazy it was. Like
literally just mayhem. It was literally
like Kevin M. It was Kevin Mallister.
I could hear the Home Alone soundtrack
playing
like
So, I was like,
I'm going to get to this question about
the insecure cast real quick. So, I was
like trying to navigate and then I
realized there's this one lady that was
just like [ __ ] up the flow for folks.
She had a carry-on and and then she had
her big ass purse and then she had these
two big bags, but the way she had them
situated was like she couldn't navigate.
And so she was slowing down the flow
because of how she was like impeding
folks. And I I stopped and I literally
just again, this doesn't always work,
but
I literally just was like, "Move this
here. Take that. Put it here. Hold these
together and this together. Go."
She was like, "Thank you."
Again, not everybody's going to be
compliant.
I don't know if compliance is the right
word. It's not, but not everybody's just
going to go along with that. But she
did,
and it freed up
the path for everyone.
I got it together.
Let's go. Okay.
We went on our way.
The bag is falling open like sis sis
sis.
Someone said you're cancer. You know
when to be instructive and demanding.
I can't wait to see my man's chart
because that is an instructive [ __ ]
You going to get some instructions.
Okay.
Someone asked, "How does he feel about
my pajamas?"
Here's the comedy.
Normally, I would just sleep naked if
I'm with my dude, but he was like, "No."
He was like, "With the AC, you need to
put something on your back cuz you'll
get sick."
Come on in.
This [ __ ] right here way
put something in your back. You're going
to get sick.
like okay
compliance
listen if it makes I ain't going to
argue if it makes sense
I ain't it is absolutely wears that
baby's hat hilarious it is absolutely
somebody put a hat on that baby why that
baby don't have a
My kitties and my doggy are great.
Sarah, if you're still here, the water
fountain and the bathroom got
disconnected somehow. I'm sure Mando is
the culprit.
Iman like [laughter]
it is always warm.
It's always warm.
But
>> so someone asked um is reconciliation
between me and the insecure cast a
possibility? And I want to just make it
clear that I do not have
issues with
majority of the insecure cast.
And my issue
with Issa is an employee is an
employment issue.
So
you know like the insecure cast is
consistent of several people
and I am
cool with the vast majority of them.
And then there's some that I don't have
any relationship with. Like it's not
it's not beef or not.
It's not even a ne, you know, there's
just like
so I'm not really sure like the
expectation here,
you know, like I'm not I'm not I'm not
I'm not sure of the expectation. And I
think that people want me to
defer or be submissive
um
to the person in charge
and
I have always deferred.
Um,
but I won't do that if I'm not being
cared for,
you know, and no one should,
right? No one should. If you don't feel
you're being cared for, the deferment
stops, you know. That's why this whole
business of like men are leaders, etc.,
etc. Like, first of all, not all men are
leaders. So, let's just start there,
okay? But let's say your man is like a
leader type person.
That is only valuable if they're leading
in a positive fashion.
When I was on Insecure,
I was always very cognizant that this is
not my show.
This is Issa's dream. This is her
vision. This is not my show.
I went and did Smart Funny and Black.
That's my show.
So, I don't need to be a leader over at
Yosho because I have my show. I am a
leader. So, it it it does
um
it does like, you [clears throat] know,
require me to to fill that space to be
in my natural rhythm. However, I don't
need to do that in someone else's space
where they are the leader.
I can go create my own space to do that.
So, I was never trying to um be the
leader in that space. I was always very
aware I was always very aware that you
know here I am a part of an ensemble. I
am an employee. I need to ask
permission.
I need to um
you know verbalize in a particular
fashion.
I would say there was there was one
instance where I feel like I came out my
face and that was in season 3 cuz I was
very upset that I was not included in
the
um in the Emmys
um panel that they had. they they had
ostracized me from that and I verbalized
my my displeasure with that and I
wouldn't say I was calm.
Um,
however that was addressed and you know
you move past that but
at the end of the day um you don't owe
your employer
the ability to disrespect you and
disregard you.
You don't owe them that. Even if they're
a black woman.
I know
you don't owe them that. Even if they're
a black woman.
So
this is it.
That's it. You're not going to
necessarily get along with all your
co-workers. How there, however, there
are very fair expectations for someone
in a leadership position
to protect you. Period.
And um at a certain point in season
five, you know, I was spoken to in a way
that I was not happy with and I
verbalized that and no attempts to
correct were made.
That's it.
But I I I you know, I had some great
times with other folks. I had some great
times with Issa. Y'all have seen the
video. That's what's always so
fascinating to me. Like for all the
Amanda seals is difficult. Like you have
literally seen
videos
of me bringing joy and delight to that
set
as the hair and makeup trailer cuz we
used to have a ball.
We used to have a ball.
[laughter]
Thank you. Thank you. Bit of Buana
giving props on my truth translator
album. Yeah, we used to have a ball in
on the with the makeup trailer and
insecure and you know Wade my husband
Derek that is my that's one of my
soulmates
y'all. I really have a home man. That's
so fascinating.
When did that how did that this is
really fascinating to me because
in the past it's always been such a like
um
a fanfare for nonsense and this ain't
been none of that.
It's just
Do you know what I'm talking about? Like
you get in these relationships and it be
like
all of this hoopla
and then you realize that the hoopla
was the thing.
So,
a part of me is literally having to
adjust
to the fact that there's no hoopla. And
that is actually the good thing.
Am I cool with Natasha?
I don't have any interactions with
Natasha. I don't have beef with her. I
don't
[ __ ] with her. Like, I have no It's just
um
It's just she was someone I did a show
with.
We had positive interactions. We had
negative interactions.
But there but there's no
I mean, but that's that's working with
people. I also want to remind y'all that
like when you're shooting a show,
you're working so long. Your hours are
insane. And like it's not even like a
sane. That's it's not a sane
environment. Your hours are crazy.
You're literally working in and out of
like a character and then back to
yourself and a character and then back
to yourself. Thank you, Dr. Carol. Thank
you. You're right. That's what I always
have to keep it keep it top of mind,
right? Um you're like sitting in the
dark, then you're in the light. It's
it's not a normal environment. And I
think people don't really understand
that. Like you're working like 14 hours.
So
the expectation that the dynamics
between people are going to be like
similar to how they would be
um like in a normal work environment are
it's it's it's a not it's it's it's not
practical.
[clears throat]
So,
you know, like you may have good days
with people, you might have like days
where they're annoying. That is a goat.
You know, like, and then you move past
it. Like I remember one time me and Jay,
I had said to him that I I didn't like
the response that he had given about me
on a on a podcast and he was like, "Oh
man, I'm sorry." Like, I definitely
wasn't trying to like come at you
sideways. I I probably could have come
up with a better response than that.
And we move on. That's it.
That's it. And then we go back to
laughing because Jay is [ __ ]
hilarious.
I really like Jay Ellis. Like as a
person, I really like Jay Ellis
and Jeanelli
and Kendrick.
You know, I'm I'm really a girls girl,
but in the case of Insecure, the the men
on the show are some of my favorites.
Um,
would I do Smart Funny and Black again?
perhaps, you know, maybe in a different
iteration. You know, you got to remember
when I was doing Smart Funny and Black,
I was like in Hollywood
and so the guests on the show
were always like rappers or comedians or
performers and like that's not my
circle.
So, it might have just been, you know,
for a time.
Have a good one. Aolio 3.
If it's not raining tomorrow morning,
I will um
I will lead us in some stretches
on my Patreon.
I love my man so much.
I just think he's so cool.
Have a good one, Diane.
Thank you, Emman. His
sun sign is a Leo. So, you know,
we're doing our best with that.
So, by the way, this right here is like
a regular occurrence on Patreon.
So, just so you know, like this is how
we start the day on Patreon on a regular
basis. If it's not a live, it'll be a
video that is doing my best to try to
start us off with some thoughtful
intention
and
um
me and Sway. I don't know about that.
Um,
hey Branson. And it's only $5 a month.
How funny is that Tiffany video I made?
[sighs]
That was someone's idea in the comments.
They were like, "You should do one of
them Netflix videos about why you ain't
on the tour." I said, "Say less."
I have Tiffany's wig, but I don't know
where I put it.
I don't know where I put it.
And so, I had to just fashion some [ __ ]
out of braid hair. Y'all,
I said they gonna tear me up for this,
but whatever. [laughter]
They going to tear me up for this hair,
but I'm going to do my best. Why this
man came over and was like, "Dad, I
think you should pull it down a little
bit here. I think you should pull I was
like, my brother, my brother in Christ.
I don't think there's anything that can
make this look right.
Let me tell you the type of situation
I'm in.
When I was making that video, he was
coloring
while food was on the stove being
cooked.
Where am I? What Narnia am I in?
Why was he coloring? Cuz he saw me
coloring while we were on while we were
on FaceTime and he was like, "I want
colored pencils.
I want to color." And so I brought him
some colored pencils.
Yes, Betty.
You know, someone here asked, "Why do
you want to go on a tour where you were
mistreated?"
And I want to just bring you guys I want
to I want to frame something for you for
yourselves.
You deserve the choice
to be in or not be in spaces you've
cultivated.
I'm going to say that again.
You deserve
the choice
to be in or not in spaces that you have
cultivated.
I am an integral part of the show
insecure
even on the basis that
the the promo picture that they used for
season two that wasn't taken by somebody
off like in HBO. I took that picture.
So I hope that you can apply that for
yourself.
You deserve the choice
to be in or not in spaces you have
cultivated.
I am a part of the cultivation of the
space of insecure. That is not arguable.
You can't that's not an opinion. There's
no there's nothing subjective to that.
I was on the show for five complete
seasons.
I put my foot in that character.
I delivered an iconic performance.
Period.
I have never disparaged the show.
And when we call
identifying
the way an employer is mistreating you
as dragging,
we are literally feeding into this
corporate nonsense that says that
corporations should own you and have
more power over you.
When I was working on Insecure, after
season two, HBO had the right to
determine
what work I did. That's the contract you
sign.
You sign a contract that says we now
essentially own you and have to give
approval for any other work that you do
in the television sector or whatever
sector that is agreed to.
So I am of the mind that if I am signing
over
my
um career
right and and and because my career is
attached to my artistry if I'm signing
over the ability
to
um
perform my craft,
Right.
I should be protected.
That's it.
When you are at a certain So on shows
they have different levels of your of
your um engagement with the show. So,
you might be an extra, you might be a
reoccurring guest star, you might be a
day player,
you might be a series regular. When you
are a series regular,
you are intrinsically attached and
contractually attached to the show.
I was a series regular for four seasons
out of five.
So
on a very basic level, if you're doing a
reunion tour,
you would extend that
to everyone.
And if there has been eye, there have
been missteps,
then at the very least you create a
space for there to be some type of
mediation or you know course correction
to happen.
And
this is not just in TV. If you cultivate
a space,
you know, that's why corporate is so
[ __ ] shitty. The fact that you can
create a company and then be removed
from it
is nuts.
And so,
you know, let's be real. Technically,
are they in their right as a corporate
entity to determine who is a part of the
tour and who's not? Technically, yes.
Which is why they were this is why this
happened this way.
I at this point try not to look things
look at things solely as technically
because I've come to really understand
that
the framework of technically is often
done is often created within the
framework of a society that does not
center care.
you know
and um with business
there has been a narrative created
around business that alleviates any
level of humanity.
It removes humanity.
So that's why you hear people say it's
just business when they're literally
eradicating someone's livelihood
and
the truth is every interaction every
interaction we have is a communal one.
It may not be intimate. It may not be
personal, but it is a communal one. We
are all in community. And when folks do
things that harm the community, they
should be held accountable. When folks
do things that uphold
um
values and um
methods that harm the community, I do
believe they should be addressed.
dishonesty,
um spite,
um
mean girl [ __ ] um misogyny,
racism, you know, all of these things
are are are
behaviors that harm the community
and have to be addressed
and that's it. So, when folks are like,
"Oh, Amanda's being messy." Amanda's
being exactly what she's always been,
which is honest.
That's it. I did not even know there
wasn't a reunion until people on this
Instagram told me. If I was not on
Instagram, I wouldn't have even known
there was a reunion.
And I again, you know, this is not about
like my feel I don't have my I don't
have like hurt feelings.
my feelings are not hurt. So that's not
the point. Um it's just it's the
principle,
you know.
Well, Ryan Shorter, throw it out there.
Maybe I'll have a thought and then I'm
going to go.
How do you hold someone accountable who
is intentionally bullying and hurting
people?
Well, I would say that you address them
directly
and when they will not respond directly,
you address them publicly.
And that's really all you can do.
If they're bullying people, then you
know they may have to get bullied.
like if they're like physically harming
people. Greetings, family goes global.
Someone had a question, so I'm going to
answer it before I go.
That's it. No, like I don't know why
this is so hard for people. know that.
You know, I think what we don't So, Ryan
Sharter asked a question about this
president and said, "I don't think
they're going to leave willingly." And I
think what what a lot of people fail to
to realize is that the president is not
in charge.
You know, there are greater forces at
work right now.
You know, that's that's that's the part
that people are failing to realize.
America is not a sovereign nation.
And so,
you know, him leaving willingly, etc.,
etc., Um,
and then planning a January 6, whatever
you see is going to be for a greater
manipulation than what it's being called
as. Does that make sense?
They may name it this. If they name it
that, know that that is not what it
actually is. That's what I mean in my
song Scio where I say they is them and
who they be is not what you think.
Anyone that you can see is not Anyone
that you can see don't run the
operation.
If you haven't listened to my album
Truth Translator, you should go check it
out.
They saw a
can't believe I fell in
front
and they don't lie to you.
It's all [singing]
Every time I post videos on YouTube of
my own video, they're like flagged. I'm
like this.
Am I still in touch with Apprentice? No.
I don't have beef with apprentice, but
I'm not in touch with her.
Anyh who, let me get a move on. Um
and uh I wish you all a great day
and
um
you would love to see me and Lil Duval
do a podcast.
What a random combo. Anyho, check out um
my Patreon. Go to my links in my bio.
Click all those links and see if any of
them spark an interest to you. There's
my store, Amanda Exports. There's my
Patreon, The Seal Squad. Um, you can
also go to my my Substack, etc. So, you
Oh, you can check out my album, Truth
Translator. Hope you all have a great
one.